LUNDE ROBIN

Cleino Anju 101, Chuo 4-5-9, Yamato-shi, 242-0021 | 080-8900-7795 | robin@keio.jp | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

I am a dedicated and reliable person with leadership experience. I love new challenges and expanding my horizon. I believe a wide platform of knowledge is important to continue personal development. My hobbies are photography and working out.

SKILLS

Computer Science

· Programming languages:

Python, C, Assembly, JavaScript, Java, Scheme, HTML, SQL, GO Bold = 2 years or more. Regular = less than 2 years

- · Undergraduate Major: Computer Security
- · Masters: Computer Security Current GPA: 3.91

Languages

· Norwegian (Native) · English (Native equivalent)

· Spanish (Beginner) · Japanese (Beginner)

Leadership

I have a lot of experience serving as a leader in different environments. In addition to my army experience, I am currently vice-president for a circle (*JES*) at my university, I have worked as a tour-guide for large groups and I have a seat on the board of a private Norwegian company (*KR Byqq Østfold AS*)

Courses

Undergraduate:

- Information Security
- Security in Operating Systems and Software
- Computer Architecture
- Systems Development
- Computer Communication
- Introduction to Operating Systems and
 - Data Communications
- Operating Systems

Graduate:

- Internet Security Architecture
- Network Security
- Ubiquitous Computing Systems
- Design Strategy (Spatial Information Systems and Architecture)

- · Functional Programming
- · Object-Oriented Programming
- Problem Solving with High-Level Languages
- · Introduction to Databases
- · Algorithms and Data Structures
- Logical methods for computer science (Discreet mathematics)
- Mathematics 1
- Conceptual Framework (Introduction to general computer science concepts)
- Advanced Research (Introduction to faculty members research
- Global Governance Studies (Globalization and Regional Transformation)

EXPERIENCE

2016.09 - 2017.01

2017.08 - Present	English teacher, School Oiso 英会話教室
-------------------	------------------------------------

English teacher for students ranging from kindergarten kids to senior citizens. I am responsible for holding classes, assisting in classes and contributing to the learning environment for the students by following up each individual and giving them guidance and examples.

2017.09 – 2018.01 Teaching Assistant: Web design and management, Keio University SFC

Help students set up, design and create webpages. Assist in leading group work in an efficient manner. I also help students with explaining technical concepts or knowledge they are lacking.

Teaching Assistant: Intro to Computer Security, Keio University SFC

2017.07 – 2018.01 Held presentations about news in computer security and explained why it was important. Also held demonstrations of common attack methods

and explained basic security concepts.

2016.01 – 2016.06 Teaching Assistant: Computer Communications, *University of Oslo*

Corrected papers and deliveries for a course teaching computer communications, an introduction to network programming done in C. The class was about creating a network daemon and routing using their

own protocol.

2014.04 – 2016.01 Tour-guide, *Mathy Travels*

Tour-guide for international tourists visiting Oslo. I was responsible for planning visits to Oslo and guiding tourists through their stay. This included organizing transport, preparing routes, checking reservations

and schedules and managing unexpected events.

2012.09 – 2013.08 Sergeant, Norwegian Armed Forces

Squad leader for two military intelligence squads (16 soldiers). My responsibilities were training and education of the squad members,

as well as leading the squads in active duty operations.

EDUCATION

2016.09 – Present Masters of Media and Governance: Cyber Informatics, Keio University SFC

2013.09 – 2016.06 Bachelor of Informatics: Programming and Networks, *University of Oslo*

2011.07 – 2012.06 UB-Jeger, Heimevernets Befalsskole (The Norwegian Home Guard's NCO school)







